

VLADIMIR KARIĆ

WEB DEVELOPER | https://devlak2001.github.io/portfolio/



+381 62 8895202







SUMMARY

Highly motivated and skilled web developer who is driven by satisfied clients. Fourth-year student at the Faculty of Technical Sciences, Department of IT, with hands-on experience in various programming languages and software tools. Strong self-learner with a track record of successful projects.

SKILLS & TECHNOLOGIES

- **Programming Languages**: C, C++, C#, Java, JavaScript, TypeScript, Python.
- Front-End Development: React, HTML, CSS (SASS), Three.js, Responsive design.
- Web APIs: DOM, Fetch, Canvas, MediaDevices, Geolocation, Sensor, Web Storage, Share, etc.
- Tools and Software: VS Code, Photoshop, Illustrator, Figma, Blender, Meta Spark Studio.
- Version control, browser/device compatibility testing, debugging, communication.

EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER • ROCK PAPER REALITY • MARCH 2022 - PRESENT

- Collaborated with a team to develop Web Augmented Reality applications.
- Utilized React library to create reusable UI components, resulting in overall increased productivity.
- Worked closely with graphic designers to ensure the app always matched the brand's guidelines.
- Successfully implemented API calls to external sources, retrieving and processing relevant information.
- Conducted Research and Development to contribute and innovate our project template.
- Designed captivating web animations aimed at enhancing user engagement.
- Handled asset optimization and browser/device testing to make sure app is accessible by everyone.

FREELANCE FRONT-END DEVELOPER • UPWORK • FEBRUARY 2021 - MARCH 2022

- Developed front-end solutions for websites, web applications and browser extensions.
- Converted design mockups into actual products, making sure everything was pixel-perfect.
- Created design mockups and coded email signatures to enhance client branding and user engagement.
- Diagnosed and resolved issues in websites created by other developers.
- Developed automation scripts to streamline repetitive tasks.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S DEGREE • 2020 - PRESENT • FACULTY OF TECHNICAL SCIENCES, SERBIA • IT DEPARTMENT. HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA • 2016 - 2020 • HIGHSCHOOL "SVETI SAVA", POŽEGA, SERBIA • IT DEPARTMENT.